The initial game information:
Robot A HP=101
Robot B HP=100
Robot Z HP=100
Z . . A . B 
Success: Robot Z shoots A
Robot A health point is reduced from 101 to 1
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot A HP=1
Robot B HP=100
Robot Z HP=100
Success: Robot Z shoots A
Robot A health point is reduced from 1 to 0
Robot A is being destroyed by Z
Z . . . . B 
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot B HP=100
Robot Z HP=100
Success: Robot Z shoots B
Robot B health point is reduced from 100 to 0
Robot B is being destroyed by Z
Z . . . . . 
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot Z HP=100
=== Game Ended ===
