The initial game information:
Robot A HP=1000
Robot B HP=300
Robot C HP=201
Robot D HP=200
Robot E HP=199
. B . 
C A D 
. E . 
Success: Robot A hits B
Robot B health point is reduced from 300 to 100
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot A HP=1000
Robot B HP=100
Robot C HP=201
Robot D HP=200
Robot E HP=199
Success: Robot A hits C
Robot C health point is reduced from 201 to 1
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot A HP=1000
Robot B HP=100
Robot C HP=1
Robot D HP=200
Robot E HP=199
Success: Robot A hits D
Robot D health point is reduced from 200 to 0
Robot D is being destroyed by A
. B . 
C A . 
. E . 
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot A HP=1000
Robot B HP=100
Robot C HP=1
Robot E HP=199
Success: Robot A hits E
Robot E health point is reduced from 199 to 0
Robot E is being destroyed by A
. B . 
C A . 
. . . 
== Health points of alive robots ==
Robot A HP=1000
Robot B HP=100
Robot C HP=1
=== Game Ended ===
